12 Hours, 4 Killers, 1 Way Out.
Tiger House is a action, crime, drama film directed by Tom Daley.
A young gymnast battles a group of bank robbers at the home of her boyfriend.
Kelly, played by Kaya Scodelario.
Callum, played by Ed Skrein.
Shane, played by Dougray Scott.
Reg, played by Brandon Auret.
Sveta, played by Langley Kirkwood.
Lynn, played by Julie Summers.
Tiger House is a 2015 action thriller film directed by Thomas Daley and
starring Kaya Scodelario, Dougray Scott, and Ed Skrein.
Scodelario stars as an injured and pregnant gymnast who must
defend her boyfriend's house against a home invasion.
The film is produced by the United Kingdom-based Glass Man
Films and the South Africa–based Tiger House Film.
The film, set in the United Kingdom, was filmed in South Africa.
Koch Media acquired distribution rights for the United Kingdom.
Tiger House was released for digital download on 24 August
2015 and on home media on 1 September 2015.
The film explores themes of fire, robbery, pregnancy, murder, teenage girl.
The tone is emotional and intense.